### Sambandha Dahal

Address: Urlabari-05, Morang

**Phone:** +977-9840723609,+974-30267703 **Email:** Sambandha.dahal10@gmail.com



#### **OBJECTIVE**

I'm an adaptable and innovative qualified Mechanical Engineer with over 10 years' experiences in Hydropower plant, Oil and gas industry and construction. Intend to build a career with leading corporate with Committed and dedicated people, which will help me to explore myself fully and release my potential. Willing to work as a key player in challenging & Creative environment. Accustomed to performing in deadline driven, fast paced environments using superior Organizational skill and outstanding work ethics.

#### **Work Experiences**

- Mechanical Engineer, Project Engineer Chainlink Engineer Pvt. Ltd 2016-2020
- i. Repair of guide vane and turbine at Trishuli Hydropower station. (2017)
- ii. Fabrication of 3- guide vane test rig Assembly at turbine Testing lab.(2017)
- iii. HVAC duct Installation of Purging Unit at American Embassy, Maharajgunj. (2018)
- iv. Supply, Delivery, Commissioning of Remotely Operated Vehicle at Kaligandagki Hydropower station.(2018/2019) (China, Charpie Intelligence Technology)
- v. Repair and Maintenance of Different gates at Devighat Hydropower station (Intake, Forebay, Tailrace) (2019)
- Design Engineer and Planner
  - S & P Innovation and Construction Pvt.Ltd 2019-2020
- Design Engineer and Planner
  - Dynamic Resources Management Services Pvt Ltd 2020-2021
- Scaffolding Designer and planner
  - MV Dugar Group, Likhu II HEP 55 MW,2021-2023
- Scaffolding Lead Man, PTW
  - Descon Engineering LLC September 2023- March 2024
- Scaffolding Supervisor
  - Descon Engineering LLC September 2024-March to present
- Scaffolding Supervisor
  - Descon Engineering LLC September 2024-March to present

Visweswarya Instititue of Technological University Bachelor in Mechanical Engineering (2012-2016)

#### **EDUCATION**

College

Kathmandu Model College (2010-2012)

School level Certificate

Saptakoshi English Boarding Higher Secondary School.

### ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITES PLANNING, SUPERVISION AND INSPECTION

- I have 10+ years' experience in Hydropower Industry, Oil & gas Industry and Petrochemicals, Building construction, Shutdown and plant Maintenance, Power station in Nepal and overseas. (China, Qatar.) Supervising and Inspection of all scaffolding activities in Overall site on day to day bases and responsibility for the scaffolding activity as per plan and scheduled to meets to the client requirements and ensuring the all scaffolding methods comply with HSE policy.
- Establishing and maintenance timely completion of scaffolding activities as per the project timelines.
- Preparing and maintaining tracking sheets during the shutdown phase.
   Coordinating with site execution team for site verification & scope clarification during pre-shutdown phase.
- Strictly implementation of erection and dismantling of scaffolding accordance with TG20:21 and other relevant codes of practice.(CITB-NVQ-UK and TUV)
- Participate in weekly management and safety walk through for any scaffold safety issue.
- Conduct tool box talk daily in the job site. Responsible for the work site area: site planning, preparation of crews, materials and work permits.
- Prepare and update project schedule based on the contract.
- Report to the Organization about the current work progress and make comparison between plan and actual progress and study impact of alternative approaches to work.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS, TRAININGS AND SKILLS**

- Primavera P6 | Primavera Institute Forum
- AUTOCAD 2D and 3D modeling
- International General Certificate in Occupational Health and Safety | NEBOSH UK
- CISRS, Basic Inspection Scaffolding
- ANSYS for Mechanical
- STADD Pro
- ETABS, Structural Analysis
- Microsoft package, Advance Excel and Microsoft project.
- Managing Safety | IOSH, UK
- Work at Height| QE LNG.
- Gas watch, QE LNG
- Permit to Work, QE LNG V7 and V9
- Confined Space Entry | QE LNG

I hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge.

Sambandha Dahal

#### COPY OF ORIGINAL Serial No. 10-1321-069

### **GOVERNMENT OF NEPAL** MINISTRY OF EDUCATION OFFICE OF THE CONTROLLER OF EXAMINATIONS

## **School Leaving Certificate Examination**

MARK - SHEET

THE MARKS SECURED BY.... SAMBANDHA DAHAL

DATE OF BIRTH...... 2052/07/21 BS ( 07- NOV- 1995 AD )

ROLL MORANG SYMBOL NO 0811113 Q

OF SAPTAKOSHI ENGLISH BOARDING HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL URLABAR

IN THE ANNUAL S.L.C. EXAMINATION OF 2066 BS (2010 AD) ARE GIVEN BELOW

SERIAL	SUBJECTS		FULL MARKS	PASS MARKS	OBTAINED MARKS		TOTAL	GRACE	REMARKS
N N					TH	PR			
01	COMP. ENGLISH		100	32	66	25	91	1000	
02	COMP. NEPALI		100	32	62	12-70	62		
03	COMP. MATHEMATICS		100	32	95		95		
04	COMP. SCIENCE		100	32	67	25	92	- 110	
05	COMP. SOCIAL STUDIES		100	32	61		61	Auto	
06	COMP. HEALTH, POP & ENV EDU			32	60	25	85	1	
07	OPT.I ADDITIONAL MATHEMATICS			32	95		95		
08	OPT.II COMPUTER SCIENCE		100	32	35	50	85		
							666		

FULL MARKS	1ST DIV WITH DISTN.	1ST DIV	2ND DIV	3RD DIV
700	The second	420	315	224
800	640	480	360	256

RESULT

FIRST DIVISION WITH DISTINCTION

- 1. # Means subject(s) appeared in the supplementary examination.
- 2. F and an asterisk (\*) Fail
- 3. A Absent
- 4. W Result withheld
- 5. C Subject Cancelled
- 6. OL Open Learning

Compgr. mark25

50

Written by

Under - Secretar

EXT

TOT.

SANOTHIMI, BHAK29JAUG-2572L DATE OF ISSUE :

# ONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION ONDARY EDUCATION NO. No. 887601648 ONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY.



(Estd. Under the Higher Secondary Education Act, 1989)

Academic Transcript

A 0881096

THE ST. ONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HI

ate of Birth: 2052/07/21 KATHMANDU MODEL H S SCHOOL, BAGBAZAR, KATHMANDU

HER SECONDARY FOUGATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY ST. Subjects are ingher secondary education board higher necondary education board higher necondary education board higher necondary education board higher necond	Full Marks	Pass Marks	Marks Secured	Remarks U ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD INCHERN CATION BOARD HIGHERN CATION BOARD HIGHER S CATION BOARD HIGHERS	ECONDARY EDUCATION BOA FAYNDARY EDUCATION BOA ECONDARY EDUCATION BOA ECONDARY EDUCATION AGAI
TAMES SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY	RY EDUCAT	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BUARD HIGHER	rade XI
English ARY EDUCATION ROARD HIGHER SECOND	100	ON BOOK BOOK BOOK BOOK BOOK BOOK BOOK BO	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	Year Year	Symbol Number
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECOND	RY 100 AT	ON BOARD ON B35RB	HIGHER SEC	ONDARÝ EDU ONDARY EDU	CAPTON BOARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY ENGLATION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD INCHER SECOND	HEY EXPLICATE	ON BUARD	RIGHER SEG	ONDARY EDU	CA 103 NOAR 2068	17600618
PHYSICS (TH) ATTON BOARD HIGHER SECOND	075	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHERN CATION BOARD HIGHERN	ECUNDARY EDUCATION BOAT ECONDARY EDUCATION ROAD
PHYSICS (PR) THON BOARD HIGHER SECOND	025	ON BOORD	HGH 25 SEC	ONDARY EDG	CATION SOARD HIGHER'S	CONDUCTS EDUCATION BOAT
CHEMISTRY (TH)	075	27	62	ONDARY EDU	CATION ROARD HIGHERS	ECONDARY EDUCATION BOA
THE CHEMISTRY D (PR) IN BOARD BIGHER SECONDA	RY E0251	ON B10rd	11GH 25SE	ONDARY EDI	CATION BOARD HIGHER'S	C ONDARY EDUCATION BOAR
BIOLOGY (TH) THON BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	075	ON B 27RD	11CH 55 SEC	ONDARY EDI	CATION BOARD HIGHER VI	CONDARY EDISCATION BOAR
BIOLOGY (PR)	025	10	25	ONDARVEDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER ST	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAD
HEMATHEMATICS CATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RV 100	ON 83540	нсн65яю	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD BUCHER SI	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY	RYEDUCAT	ON BOARD:	HICHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD DIGHERS	CONDARY PRECATION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDS	RY EDUCAT	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	CINDARY EDI	CATION BOARD BEGIER SI	CONDARY EDUCATION ROAD
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER ST	CONDARY EIGH STRON BOAD
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD RIGHER SECONDARY BUCKER SECONDARY	RY EDUCAT	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER SI	COMPARY FIRST ATTON BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	500	ON BOARD	396	ONDARY EDU	CATION ROARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY FINE STION ROAD
rade XII ONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECOND	RY EDUCAT	ON BUARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHERG	rade XII EDUCATION BOAL
HER Englishary EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDIT	CATION BOARD INCHERS	CONDUCTION BOOK
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHT SEC	ONDARY EDU	CALION BOARD BIGHER SI	Symbol Number
Nepali Nepali	100	35	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER SE	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAT
TER SECONDARY FIRST ATTOM BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDDUAL	ON BOARD	ПСН74	UNDARY EDU	CA TON BOAR 2069 ERS	27600596
PHYSICS (TH) TON BOARD BIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDG	CATION BOARD HIGHER ST	FUNDARY FOLE STION BOAR
PHYSICS (PR) TION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	075	ON BALED	HIGH46 SEC	ONDARVEDU	UATION BOARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAR
CHEMISTRY (TH) ON HOARD BIGHER SECONDA	7 (88, 98)	ON NOTED	HIGH25 SEC	ONDARY EDI	CATION BOARD HIGHER S	CONDARY FIRST ATTON BOAT
CHEMISTRY (PR)	075	ON BULED	HIGHERE	ONDARY EDE	CA <del>TION BOARD HIGHER ST</del>	CONDARY LIBER AFTON BOAR
HEMATHEMATICS CATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	025	ON BIORD	HIGHESSEC	ONDARY EDU	CALION BOARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY COLUMNION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDIT CATION BOARD, BIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDI	CATION ROARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD. HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER SI	CONDARY EDG: ATRON BOAR
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDLE	TATION BOARD HIGHER SE	CONDARY EDUCATION BOAS
TER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY FRUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDL	TATION BOARD HIGHER ST	CONDARY LUTE ATTON BOAR
BUR SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD, HIGHER SECONDA	RYEDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDL	AFION BOARD BEGIEF ST	CONDURY FIGURATION BOAT
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDU	CATION BOARD HIGHER ST	CONDARY EDIT CTION BOAR CONDARY EDIT CTION BOAR
DER SECUSIONARY EDUCATION BOARD. HIGHER SECONDA	RY EDUCATI	ON BOARD	HIGHER SEC	OND SRY EDGE	ATION BOARD HIGHER SE	CONDUCT PRICATION BUAN
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD, HIGHER SECONDA	RYEDUCATE	ON ROARD	HIGHER SEC	ONDARY EDD	Percentage of agg	egate marks secured in
HER SECONDARY ED Total ON BOARD HIGHER SECONDA	500	ON BOARD .	372	ONDARY EDLE	Grade XI and XII	76.80 Secured III
HER SECONDARY EDUCATION BOARD THICHER SECONDA	RYTDUCATI		HIGHER SEC		Division: Distin	CIACIL BY STREET OF STREET
HER SECONDA Grand Total ARD HIGHER SECONDA	1000		768	CALLES AND THE PARTY OF	DIVIDION HIERTIF	CTION

(Deputy Controller)

ON BOARD HIGHER SECONDARY EDI

ATTON BOARD | Controller of Examinations

rading System:

5% and above - Distinction 0% and above - First division 5% and above - Second division

5% and above - Pass division

HIGHER SECOTO pass the examination candidates must secure HER SEC 35% marks in theory and 40% marks in practical HICK STOC papers, separately, ROARD HIGHER STOD

> Note: \* means a student has passed in the second attempt. means a student has passed in more than two attempts.



### COPY OF ORIGINAL Serial No. 10-1321-069

### GOVERNMENT OF NEPAL MINISTRY OF EDUCATION OFFICE OF THE CONTROLLER OF EXAMINATIONS

## **School Leaving Certificate Examination**

MARK - SHEET

THE MARKS SECURED BY.... SAMBAI

SAMBANDHA DAHAL

DATE OF BIRTH...... 2052/07/21 BS ( 07- NOV- 1995 AD )

ROLL

MORANG

SYMBOL NO.

0811113 Q

OF SAPTAKOSHI ENGLISH BOARDING HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL URLABAR

IN THE ANNUAL S.L.C. EXAMINATION OF 2066 BS (2010 AD)

.....ARE GIVEN BELOW

SERIAL	SUBJECTS	FULL MARKS	PASS MARKS	OBTAINED MARKS		TOTAL	GRACE	REMARKS
				TH	PR		A M	REN
01	COMP. ENGLISH	100	32	66	25	91		
02	COMP. NEPALI	100	32	62		62		
03	COMP. MATHEMATICS	100	32	95		95		
04	COMP. SCIENCE		32	67	25	92		
05	COMP. SOCIAL STUDIES		32	61		61		
06	COMP. HEALTH, POP & ENV EDU	100	32	60	25	85		
07	OPT.I ADDITIONAL MATHEMATICS	100	32	95		95		
08	OPT.II COMPUTER SCIENCE	100	32	35	50	85		
FULL M	ARKS 1ST DIV 1ST DIV 2ND DIV 3RD DIV	CD	AND TOT	A1		666		

224

256

1. # Means subject(s) appeared in the supplementary examination.

420

480

2. F and an asterisk (\*) - Fail

WITH DISTN.

640

3. A - Absent

700

800

- 4. W Result withheld
- 5. C Subject Cancelled
- 6. OL Open Learning

Compgr. mark25 INT. EXT.

TOT.

50

Written by

315

360

RESULT

Under - Secretar

83.25%

FIRST DIVISION

WITH DISTINCTION

SANOTHIMI, BHAK29-7416-2572L

DATE OF ISSUE :



### ವಿಶ್ವೇಶ್ವರಯ್ಯ ತಾಂತ್ರಿಕ ವಿಶ್ವವಿದ್ಯಾಲಯ, ಬೆಳಗಾವಿ

VISVESVARAYA TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY, BELAGAVI
KARNATAKA, INDIA

P 03733

Provisional Degree Certificate

This is to certify that Mr./Ms. SAMBANDHA DAHAL

is qualified for the award of the degree of BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING (Mechanical Engineering of this University for having passed the prescribed examination held during January 2017in Second Class with University Seat No. 1RI12ME046

The degree will be conferred on him | her at the next convocation or thereafter.

Belagavi Date :

Date: 10 AUG 2017



Registrar (Evaluation)

नेपाल सरकार GOVERNMENT OF NEPAL Seri

Serial No.

10-1322-069



# शिक्षा मन्त्रालय MINISTRY OF EDUCATION परीक्षा नियन्त्रण कार्यालय OFFICE OF THE CONTROLLER OF EXAMINATIONS





## प्रवेशिका परीक्षा School Leaving Certificate Examination

# प्रमाण-पत्र Certificate

This is to certify that SAMBANDHA DAHAL, a student of
SAPTAKOSHI ENGLISH BOARDING HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL URLABARI
Roll
Examination held in the year 2066 BS (2010 AD) in the
FIRST WITH division. According to the record of this office,
his/her date of birth is 2052/07/21 BS ( 07- NOV- 1995 AD )
Symbol No. 0811113 Q
Date of issue: 29-Aug-2012
Sanothimi, Bhaktapur Written by Checked by Verified by



# तिपाल इिंठाितियरिङ्ग परिषद् े Nepal Engineering Council साधारण दर्तावाला इन्जिनियरको नाम दर्ताको प्रमाणपत्र



कोशी अंचल मोरङ्ग जिल्ला उर्लाबा	रीनगरपालिका ∕ गाउँ पालिका, वडा नं	ox बस्ने जन्म मिति २०४२/०७/२१ को
श्री सम्बन्ध दाहाल लाई		
किताबमा नाम दर्ता गरी नेपाल इन्जिनियरिङ्ग परिषद्	ऐन, २०५५ को दुष्टा १६ तथा नेपाल इन्जिनियरिङ	परिषद् नियमावली, २०५७ को नियम ११ को
उपनियम (१) वा नियम १४ बमोजिम यो नाम दर्ताको प्रमाण	ापत्र दिइएको छ्वा वरिङ परिक	
दर्ता नम्बर: ३०९४ "मेकानिकल" "क" वर्ग		9 11102/
नाम दर्ताको प्रमाणपत्र जारी भएको मितिः २०७४/०७/२८	( Tole ) *	हस्ताक्षरः देण्याच्ये
V===/, V-	परिषद्को छाप	नामः इ. खम राज जाशा
0	काठभ	रजिष्ट्रार
CERTIFICATI	E FOR REGISTERED ENG	INEERS
As per the resolution of the Council dated	ed this Certificate in accordance with section 16 of	ipality/Village Council, ward No
14/11/2017 Issued On:	Seal of Council	Signature: Er. Khem Raj Joshi Name: